triathloninspires.com 2016-09-30

# Triathlon Inspires | Inspiration Beyond Limits!

**Google translations (NOT 100% accurate)**.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following information outlines our privacy policy. 

At TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com, we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We want to assure our users that TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com will not willfully disclose any specific individual information about you to any third party unless you give us your express permission to do so.

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Accordingly, children under 13 years old may be restricted from participating in certain activities on TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com, However, TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com, does not knowingly obtain, retain or use information from anyone who indicates that they are under 13 years old. If you would like more information about TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com’s, policy for collecting information from children, please read our Note to Parents below.

Please read this Privacy Policy ("Policy") for an explanation of how we will treat your personal information. By using TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com, you consent to the collection and use of personal information as outlined in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our site. If we make any material changes to the Policy, those changes will be posted here so that you are always aware of what personal information is collected, how that information is used, and under what circumstances that information may be disclosed. Since this Policy may change from time to time, you should check back periodically. Your continued use of TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com following the posting of changes to the Policy will signal your acceptance of such changes.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Policy, please contact info@triathloninspires.com

## 

TABLE OF CONTENTS

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the site.

2\. The organization collecting the information.

3\. How the information is used.

4\. With whom the information may be shared.

5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.

## 

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the site.

As stated above, TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Please review our Note to Parents, if you have any questions regarding our Policy with respect to children. 

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com does not collect personally identifiable information through the site unless you provide that information during registration for various features on the site. Information required to participate in such features may vary but will typically include your first and last name; address including city, state, zip code and country; complete date of birth; phone number; and e-mail address. You may also be requested to provide a username and password for certain features. TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com will maintain all of the personal information submitted by you in secured servers behind corporate firewalls.

## 

2\. The organization collecting the information.

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com is operated by Triathlon Inspires, L.L.C. located in Miami, FL. info@triathloninspires.com for more information.

## 

3\. How the information is used.

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com may use information provided at registration or information obtained through third parties to offer better-targeted products and services to you. We use targeting to customize and enhance your online experience on the site. The use of information provided at registration or obtained through third parties will not be provided to advertisers or partners, except in aggregate form, unless you have consented to such use at registration. 

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com uses "cookie" technology. Cookies are pieces of information transferred to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Such technology is an industry standard and is used by most major Web sites. TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. In order to effectively use the site and some of its features, your browser must accept cookies. 

Users should be aware that TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com can not control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept cookies; however, users should note that cookies might be necessary to provide the user with certain features available on TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com.

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com tracks certain general usage pattern information, including what pages people visit and how long they have been registered users. TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com may log users' IP addresses (the group of four numbers separated by periods, such as 123.45.64.89, that identifies a particular host computer) for the purposes of system administration, site tracking and reporting of aggregate usage information to our marketing and product development teams.

From time to time, TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com may solicit your opinion to determine your preferences and dislikes in order to provide you with a better product. These surveys are always optional to the user and your decision not to participate in a survey will not affect your status as a TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com user. Should you choose to participate, any information you give us may be used in aggregate form for marketing purposes, and to enhance your overall experience on our site. 

## 

4\. With whom the information may be shared.

Once again, TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com will not provide any personally identifiable information, other than to its affiliates, about you to advertisers or other partners without your consent. As stated above, TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com may, however, provide advertisers and/or other partners with anonymous aggregated information about our users to illustrate trends and patterns. All third parties with whom we share such information will have independent privacy and data collection practices and TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com has no responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

We will never give out any information linking your real name to your screen name unless you authorize us to do so, or unless required to do so by law.

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com has several partners that can offer valuable products and services to our members. From time to time, TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com may give or sell a list from our database of users to these third party vendors. These lists will consist of only those users that have "opted in" to receiving special offers and promotions during the initial registration process. TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that every marketing offer sent to an TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com user as a result of the provision of such information contains a link for that user to no longer receive such offers. In addition, we may share your information with a company that acquires all or substantially all of TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com’s assets or in a merger or acquisition, but only if such company agrees to abide by this Privacy Policy.

While TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com is careful in choosing its partners and advertisers, we are only responsible for content on our own site. All third parties associated with TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com (including, but not limited to, advertisers, sponsors and other Internet sites) with whom we share information have independent privacy and data collection practices. TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com does not control this collection of information and is neither responsible nor liable for their independent policies or actions.

## 

5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

You are not required to receive any mailings that you do not wish to receive. By visiting our website, you will have the option to sign up to receive newsletters and selected sponsor offers and discounts. You will not receive such information if you do not select such options. If, after you choose to receive such information, you wish to discontinue receiving these items, you may change your subscription preferences by following the instructions provided within the e-mails received.

## 

6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.

Only those employees needed to carry out the business functions will have access to information on individual TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com customers. We train each such employee with respect to the TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com Privacy Policy, and those violating these policies will be subject to disciplinary action.

It is important to remember that whatever you transmit or disclose online can be collected and used by others or unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. In addition, we may disclose information to law enforcement or other government officials if we determine such disclosure to be appropriate, or if we are compelled to disclose it by court order or operation of law.

Any information voluntarily disclosed by users and posted on our site (on message boards and/or in chat areas) may be viewed and used by others. If users post personal information that is accessible to the public online, the user does so at his or her own risk. Users accept that they may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

LAST UPDATED: July 3th, 2014

Copyright 2014 Triathlon Inspires. All rights reserved.

Use of this site signifies your acceptance of the TERMS OF USE.

## 

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com NOTES TO PARENTS

It is Triathlon Inspires and/or TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com’s policy not to solicit any personally identifiable information from children. A number of interactive features on TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com require registration to participate (e.g., e-mail newsletters, Athlete Online Form, etc.) All registrants will be required to enter their full name, birth date, zip code and e-mail address. In some cases, users will be required to select a special user name to be used as an identifier for the feature and must also enter a password and a secret hint that will help us verify their identity if they forget their password. If TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com determines that a person is under the age of 13, based on the information provided during the online registration process, that person will not be permitted to register for features requiring the submission of personal information, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Instead, when a child under 13 years old tries to register for such features on TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com, he or she will be directed to content which does not involve the submission of personal information. Any personally identifiable information that the child may have attempted to enter during the registration process will not be collected or maintained by TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com.

TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com works with (and may provide links to) third party sites that offer features described on TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com. Such third parties may permit children under the age of 13 to register for these features on their sites in accordance with their respective privacy policies. Registration for these features is pursuant to the privacy policies of the third parties operating the websites on which registration occurs. For more information, please review the privacy policies of each respective third party site. TRIATHLONINSPIRES.com does not knowingly obtain, retain or use information from anyone who indicates that they are less than 13 years old.

## 

The following information outlines our privacy policy. 

• Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.

• We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

• We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

• We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

• Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

• We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

• We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

• We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Triathlon Inspires requests your previous written authorization before we will use any pictures, names, likenesses or other personal information on our website. All information is used openly on our site and is available to all users of and visitors to our site.

## 

The following information outlines our privacy policy. 

Triathlon Inspires does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect others or ours rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## 

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## 

English Language

The English version of this Privacy Policy governs. All disputes, claims and causes of action (and related proceedings) will be communicated in English.

## 

Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## 

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we make a material change to our privacy policies and procedures as to the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information, we will post a notice of those changes on our Website or notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it, prior to the change becoming effective. You are bound by changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the site after those changes have been posted. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
